目覚めては繰り返す
Day after day, I awake in a daze,
mezamete ha kurikaesu nemui asa ha
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
眠い朝は
襟のタイをきつく締め
And fasten my collar tightly.
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
教室のドアくぐると
As I walk through the door to my classroom,
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to hon no sukoshi
教室のドアくぐるとほんの少し
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I have the slightest bit of pride.
mune wo hatte arukidaseru
胸を張って歩き出せる
Then a wind rushed through that normal, everyday life.
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
そんな日常に
吹き抜ける風
聞こえた気がした　感じた気がしたんだ
I have a feeling I can hear it,
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I have a feeling I can sense it,
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
震えだす 今この胸で
Beginning to tremble within my chest.
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す今この胸で
I have a feeling it's on its way,
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
As the millions of stars began to disappear,
ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I sent them on their way,
miokutta
見送った
見送った 手を振った
Waving my hand,
te wo futta
手を振った
良かったねと
Whispering, "Congratulations".
yokatta ne, to
よかったね、と
Loitering out so late, as a group...
皆で夜遊び
It seems... I will need to punish you.
なら　お仕置きね
どういうことだ　奏
What is this about, Kanade?
Hey, what's going on here?
ねぇ　これってどういうこと
天使はもう無害じゃなっかたの
Hasn't Tenshi become harmless?
No. That's not Kanade.
違う　あいつは奏じゃない
Kanade would never just attack us.
奏は無抵抗な俺たちには刃を向けたりなんかしなかった
God damn it!
くっそーーッ　ゆりっぺ　どうすればいい
Yurippe! What do you need us to do?!
Everyone, surround her and fire as one!
皆　半円に取り囲め　集中砲火だ
Huh? Why are you commanding us?
えッ　なぜきさまが指示を取ってる　何様のつもりだ
「ディストーション」で曲げられようが　いくらか当てる
At this point it doesn't even matter if she uses Distortion!
おいよ
Right!
離せ
了解
You got it!
Step away, Yuri!
離れろ　ゆり
Fire!
撃て
くそ
Damn it!
Infirmary (Closed Off)
Is Kanade all right?
奏は大丈夫なのか
She's pretty deeply wounded, isn't she?
かなり深い傷だろ
She's the same as us.
私たちと同じよ
致命傷でも直治るわ
Even if it was fatal, she'll heal eventually.
What does it mean for there to be two of the same person running around?
同じやつが二人って　どういうことだよ
そんな訳わかんない世界になっちまったのか
Has this world turned out to be some kinda screwed-up place?
理由はあるわ
There is a cause.
What is it?
どんな
天使エリアへの侵入ミッション　覚えてる
Remember our Tenshi Domain Infiltration Mission?
Yeah.
うん
彼女のマシンにスキルを開発するソフトがあったでしょう
On her machine there was a program that creates skills, remember?
その中に　見たことのない能力がいくつかあった
In it were several skills that we haven't seen before.
One of those, Harmonics, is what she used.
その一つ　「ハーモニックス」っていうスキルが発動していたのよ
「ハーモニックス」
"Harmonics"? What kind of skill is that?
どんな能力なんだ
Were you not looking at the screen?
画面見てなっかたの
一体が二つに分かれるスキルだったわ
It's a skill where her body becomes two.
要は分身よ
In other words, cloning.
Cloning?!
分身
In other words, it's another skill that
Tenshi created herself using the software.
つまりはそれも天使自身がソフトウェアで
開発したスキルということですか
Still, I wouldn't say they were just alike.
しかし　さっくりそのままじゃないって感じだったぜ
Unlike this one here, she was aggressive. Why is that?
こいつと違って好戦的だ　なぜだ
Kanade only uses skills to protect herself. Even her sword is made that way!
奏は自分を守るための能力しか使わない
刃にしたってそうだ　兆弾させるためだ
She uses it to deflect bullets.
まったく　無能の集団だな　貴様ら
Honestly, you really are a group of blockheads.
もちろん　音無さん以外ですが
Excluding you, of course, Otonashi-san.
Fundamentally, we're a group of dumbasses.
基本　アホな集まりですから
Allow me to reveal one possibility.
可能性を一つ教えてやろう
その分身を発生させた理由が
What if the clone had been created during a time when great offensive instincts were in effect?
強い攻撃の意識を持っていた時だったとしたら
You mean that moment?
あの時ね
なるほど
I see. So she's acting out her master's sentiments from that moment.
その時の本体の命令に今も従い続けてるってことか
でも　奏が強い攻撃の意識を持つことなんてない
But Kanade would never become
overwhelmed with such offensive instincts.
どうでもいいけど　あなたやけにこの子を庇うのね
Not that it really matters, but you really stand up for her, don't you?
そりゃ　可哀相だろう
Well, don't you feel bad for her?
Look, whatever.
まぁっ　いいけど
So, what's the problem that we're really facing?
で　今の問題はなんだっけ
Should it be how to fight against Tenshi's clone?
天使の分身と戦う方法か
You idiot! It's about how to eliminate her.
馬鹿か　消す方法だ
What did you say?
なんだと
But if she willingly created her,
何してる　放しやがれ
しかし　その子が意図的に出したのなら
What's that?! Let go of me!
shouldn't she be able to willingly eliminate her?
意図的に消すことだってできるはずだろう
目覚めるのを待ってればいいだけではないのか
Shouldn't we just wait for her to wake up?
Hold on.
待って　意図的に消せたのなら
If she were capable of eliminating her willingly, would she be here right now in bed?
こうしてやられてるか
おそらく無意識での出現ね
I'm thinking it was an unconscious summoning.
That's why she couldn't eliminate her.
だから　彼女には消せなかった
It's also why she had to stop her like that, even if it ended up as a double kill.
刺し違えてでも殺るしかなかったのよ
Hey, hey, hold on a sec.
おいおい　ちょっと待ってよ
あれが消えねぇって
If she can't be eliminated,
あんなのが居続ける世界になるのかよ
that means this world's gonna be stuck with her, doesn't it?
She's overlooking us right now.
今は見逃されてはいるけど　明日からは許されない
But starting tomorrow,
「模範的」な行動から外れたら
she could pick a bloody fight against anyone who acts against the role model ideals.
すぐさま昨日のような血生臭い戦闘になる
Even though she's not the student council president any more?
生徒会長でもないのに
Yes. Her goal in disciplining us has been taken over by this copy.
ええ　私たちを更正させようという意志は立派に継承されている
さらに　好戦的　最悪ね
And she's entirely aggressive on top of that.
Just what we need.
対抗しようにも時間が無さすぎるぜ
There's not enough time even if we wanted to put up a fight.
Buy me some time.
少し時間を頂戴
How do we make that time?
どうやってその時間を作る
授業に出て　そして受ける振りをして
Attend your classes, and pretend you're listening.
先生の話には耳を決して傾けないで
Don't listen to a word the teacher says.
授業をまともに受けたら消える
If you take the class seriously, you'll disappear.
Obsess over something else and
make sure the clone doesn't catch you doing it.
分身にばれないように　とにかく別の作業に没頭すること
そして一日持ち堪えて
Last through the day like that.
だれ一人消えずに再び会えることを祈るわ
I look forward to seeing you all again, without anyone missing.
Scrapbook
Geez. Yes, yes, I know you split.
もう　分かれるのは分かったわよ
Girls' Dormitory
Tenshi's Domain
But is there a way to get rid of the other one?
どうにか消えないかしら　片方を
「エンジェル　プレイヤー」
Angel Player?
It's the manual for the software.
ソフトのマニュアルね
くっそ　この分厚さで全部英語
Damn it. It's so thick, and everything is in English.
Like I need this under such time constraints...
唯でさえ時間がないってのに
Let's see...
えーっと
Oh, it came up.
あ　高が跳ね上がった
これは距離か
This must be the distance.
Not what I need.
意味ないわね
うん
What is this?
なにこれ
All right! This is it!
やった　これだ
It was supposed to follow this command and disappear.
本来　この命令に繋がって勝手に消えるはずだったんだ
Then what's the condition for the command?
じゃあ　その発生条件は何
Ugh, I can't figure this out.
分からない
いっそパソコンごと壊してしまおうか
Should I just break the PC?
アホか　それじゃあ分身は消えない
You dumbass. That's not going to eliminate the clone.
Oh, fine! I'll just rewrite it with a program that I know!
あ　もう　分かるプログラムに書き換えてやる
Disappear already! Time Wait set for 10 seconds!
とっとと消えろう
タイムウェートは１０秒
Go!
どうだ
Ten seconds is pretty long if you're actually waiting for it to pass.
１０秒って待ってると長いわねぇ
Why can't it be set at less than 10?
なんで１０秒以下には設定できないの
All right, I think that does it.
よし　何とかなったわね
うん　なにこれ
What's this?
増えてる？
There's more than before?
「ハウリング」？
"Howling"?
Did the clone create these?
分身の方が作ったのかしら
Should I erase them?
消してしまうか
No, I've snuck into the program, so I need to limit myself to minimal editing.
いや　ここまで周到にやってきたんだ
最小限の修正に止めないと
これでよし
There we go.
あとはあの子がもう一度「ハーモニックス」を使ってくれれば
Now, if she uses Harmonics again,
「アブソーブ」のスキルが発動して
Absorb will automatically kick in and the clone will return to the host body.
分身は本体に戻る
Damn it...
しくった
どこかに出掛けたんじゃないの
Maybe she went out for a walk!
No, that's unlikely.
いや　それはない
奏は約束したんだ　俺たちと一緒いるって
Kanade promised that she'd stay with us.
そんな約束したの
You two made that promise?
Y-Yeah.
あ　ああ
The way things look, I can only imagine that she was abducted.
この乱れ様は攫われたとしか思えない
貴様　なにをした
What did you do?
"You"? Nothing more than rewrite the program.
キサマって
ブログラムの書き換え
もう一度あの子が同じ力を使えば
If she uses the same skill,
the program I added in will activate and the clone should return to the host.
追加した能力が発動して分身は本体に戻るはずだった
That's possible?
そんなことができたんですか
付け焼刃だけどね
It's only a temporary measure.
But she took action much quicker than I anticipated.
でも敵の行動が予想以上に速かった
あの子を隠されたら撃つ手がない
I can't do anything if the clone hides her.
What are we going to do?
どうするんだ
探すしかないじゃない
Search for her, obviously.
While avoiding the looming threat of that evil Tenshi?
凶悪な天使の目を逃れつつ…　ですか
It's pain enough pretending to listen to the lecture.
授業を受ける振りでさえ　やっとだったのによ
I wonder how long the diversion will last.
陽動がどれだけ持つか
Huh, "diversion"? You mean me?
陽動って私ですか
お前何のために「ガルデモ」入ったんだよ
What did you join GirlDeMo for?
岩沢さんに憧れて
Because I wanted to be like Iwasawa-san.
「ガルデモ」は陽動のためにあんだよ
But GirlDeMo exists as our diversion.
いやいやいや　あんな怖いのを相手に陽動なんてできないですって
No way! We can't divert such a terrifying enemy!
You will!
しろよ
何様じゃあ　お前
Who do you think you are?!
ここじゃ先輩だけと　なに？！逆ギレ？！
I'm an upperclassman! Do you have a problem with that?!
先輩かぁ　すみませんでしたぁ
Oh, so you're an upperclassman! I'm so sorry!
あの　ライブ中漏らすかもしれませんが　やってみます
Um, I may wet myself during the performance, but I'll do my best!
決意はありがたいけど　まだいいわ
Thank you for your determination, but it isn't needed yet.
まず　今できることをしましょう
To start off, let's do what we can.
総員に通達　天使の目撃情報を集めて
Everyone! Gather information about Tenshi sightings.
Hey yo, check this out.
It's the moonwalk. It's the moonwalk.
It's a head spin.
Gym Interior
迅速に集められた情報から
Based on the information we've gathered,
幽閉場所は「ギルド」の可能性が高いとわかったわ
there's a high possibility that she's confined at the Guild.
となれば　その最深部ね
So we'll head to the deepest recess.
あの爆破した場所にか
Wasn't that place completely destroyed?
そっ　トラップも稼働したまま
Yes. The place furthest from here,
もっとも危険でもっともここから離れた場所ってことね
where all the traps along the way are still functioning. The most dangerous place.
We're descending down there again?
またここに潜れってかよ
前回はほぼ壊滅状態だぜ
Last time, we pretty much got annihilated.
ふん　なにを臆してるんだ
What's there to fear?
真っ先に死んでたろう　お前
You were the first to die...
皆さんのために漏らしながらでも歌い続けます
I will continue to sing for everyone's sake, even if I wet myself.
根性を見せます
I'll show you what I'm made of!
Any diversion would be killed by her in an instant.
あんなのにかかっちゃあ　陽動も瞬殺よ
今回は陽動なし正々堂々と行くわよ
We won't have any diversion this time.
We'll go in fair and square.
天使と戦いながらか
So we'll be fighting Tenshi as we go along, this time.
Yes.
そっ
いい
Listen up. Our mission is to make it to the deepest recess of the Guild and rescue the original Tenshi.
作戦は「ギルド」を降下して
その最深部に行って無事天使のオリジナルを保護すること
オペレーションスタート
Operation, start!
Looks like all the old traps were left as they were. Lucky.
前のトラップはそのまま放置されてるな　ラッキー
Passage to the Guild B4
Um, if we meet Tenshi at a place like this, I think I'll wet myself anyway.
あのー　こんなところで天使に出くわしたら
どの道漏れそうなんですけど
構わん
No one cares.
構ってくださいよ
Please do care!
構わん
Go ahead.
構ってくださいよ
At least try to stop me!
さっそく現れたわね
Here she is.
撃て
Fire!
Damn, she's fast!
くそ　速えー
まだハンドガンがある
We still have handguns!
Guard Skill: Distortion.
ガードスキル「ディストーション」
Fire!
確固射撃
意外と早くけりが付けそうね
We may settle this faster than anticipated.
なに
Wh...at?
これ　どういうこと
What's going on?!
オリジナルか
That the original?
No, she's a clone, too!
違う　こいつも分身だ
Why is there another one?!
なぜ　もう一体いる
要は敵が増えているということですか
Basically, our enemy is multiplying.
On another note, he was the first to die again.
どうでもいいが　また真っ先にやられたな　あいつ
くそ
Damn... Fire!
撃て
What about the one behind us?!
後ろはどうすんだよ
それどころじゃないでしょ
We don't have the time to worry about her!
We need to focus on what's in front of us!
まずは目の前の敵よ
You look busy.
忙しそうね
Yurippe, we're running out of ammo!
ゆりっぺ　もう残弾が
There's no way to win this.
勝ち目なんてない
We'll close off the doorway.
入り口を塞ぐわ
Follow me!
付いて来なさい
Let's go!
行くわよ
ゆり
Yuri!
Ten more seconds!
あと１０秒
間に合わなかったものは残して行く
Those that don't make it in time will have to be left behind!
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six,
five, four, three,
two, one...
Zero!
There were two aggressive Tenshi...
あんな凶暴な天使が二体
Passage to the Guild B5
前の降下作戦より質が悪いぜ
This is worse than our last Parachute Mission.
なんで二体目が
Why is there a second one?
分身は「ハンドソニック」も「ディストーション」も使うのよ
The clones can use Hand Sonic and Distortion as well,
so it makes sense that she could use Harmonics.
つまり　「ハーモニックス」だって使えるってこと
Honestly, you guys are really lacking in the brain department.
まったく低能のやつらだな
もちろん　音無さん以外ですが
Excluding you, of course, Otonashi-san.
ボクが問題点を纏めてやろう
Allow me to summarise the key issues for you all.
Please do.
よろしく
問題は二つある
There are two problems.
まず何体分身が作られたのか
First, how many clones are there?
分身が分身を作れるなら
If a clone can create more clones,
then there is no limit to the number.
数に限界はない
So forget just two, you're saying there could be ten or twenty of them?
じゃあ二体どころか
十体や二十体それ以上いるかもしれねぇってか
待ってよ
But wait, Yuri added a skill. Shouldn't the clones be returning to the original host?
でも　ゆりが能力を追加している
分身は本体に戻るようになったんだろう
消えるのを待っていればいいんじゃないのか
Shouldn't we just wait for them to disappear?
That is the second problem.
それが二つ目の問題なんです
What if the clones were mass-produced before that ability was added?
もしその能力を追加するよりも先に
分身を大量生産していたとしたら
Then, you mean...!
ちょっ　そいつは
ふふ　愚民ども
So you've finally noticed, you lowlifes.
ようやく気づいたか
Oh, but you're noble of course, Otonashi-san.
もちろん　音無さんは気高い貴族でありますが
Listen up. What if she anticipated us marching in here,
いいか
僕たちがここに乗り込んでくることが分かっていて
and stationed her mass-produced clones on the way to the Guild?
すでに分身を量産し
この「ギルド」に配置させていたとしたら
That'd be a...
そりゃあ
Trap...
Exactly. A trap.
そう　ワナだ
すでに背後に二体いる
We already have two on our backs.
こいつらは消えないし　貴様らに勝ち目はない
They won't disappear, so you guys have no chance of winning.
そして　この先もうようよいるだろう
And I'm sure there'll be many waiting for us up ahead.
So we've been trapped...
閉じ込められたということか
We can't even replenish our weapons.
武器の補充もできぁしねえんだぞ
So we're just going to wait here to get killed?
やられるのを待つだけじゃねえか
What does she want to achieve by doing all this?
こんなことまでして　なにが目的なんだ
最終的には完全なる服従でしょう
Ultimately, I imagine she wants perfect obedience.
それが彼女の使命だもの
That's her mission, after all.
大人しく消えろってことかよ
So we have no choice but to disappear?
What a great way to get rid of us all at once.
俺達を一掃するには最高の作戦だな
Let's move on.
行くわよ
There's another one.
また現れた
Passage to the Guild B10
三体目かよ
A third one...
It's a waste of bullets.
弾がもったいなかろう
おい
何する気だ
What are you going to do?
Matsushita Fifth!
松下五段
行け
Go! Go while I'm still conscious!
俺の意識があるうちに行け
Why do you have to spout lines like a hero about to die?!
なんだよ　その死に際だけいいやつみたいなセリフ
Hurry up! We need to get going, now!
急いで
いまのうち行くわよ
Yeah.
あ
耐えろよ　松下五段
Hang in there, Matsushita Fifth!
あとは任せたぞ　皆
I leave the rest to you, everyone...
I won't let Matsushita-kun's death be in vain.
松下君の犠牲は無駄にしない
彼のおかげで分かったんだけど
Passage to the Guild B11
But he has proven that his method is the best way to move on.
先に進むにはあれが一番いい方法なのよ
天使はカラダが小さいから
Tenshi is small, so that's the best way to stop her from moving around.
動きを封じるにはあれが一番
いくら天使が馬鹿力でも
No matter how strong Tenshi is, a judo lock will work.
柔道の押さえ込みなら通用する
松下君に教わった柔道が生きる日が来たわね
It's time to utilise the judo we've learned from Matsushita-kun.
ええっ
In other words, we can get by with one victim per Tenshi.
つまり　一体につき一人の犠牲で済む　ということですね
"Get by with one victim"...
犠牲で済むって
And if we save the original, we can save all the victims.
そしてアタシたちがオリジナルを助け出せれば
彼らも助け出せる
Let's hurry.
急ぎましょう
四体目
There's the fourth one.
Passage to the Guild B12
It's my turn.
Get chance and luck.
ティーケー
T.K.!
おい　なんだよ　この少年漫画の最終回近い展開は
Hey! Why is this turning out like the final chapter of a shounen manga?!
いいから　どんどん行くわよ
Never mind that. Move out!
To show off my body... this is the moment!
この肉体
見せる時がきたようですね
高松
Takamatsu!
びびってられるかってんだ
I can't chicken out.
Fujimaki!
藤巻
浅はかなり
How unwise.
浅はかなりーーッ！
How unwise!
椎ちゃん
Shiina!
Just now, you've come to a sudden realisation.
さあ　きづくんだ
お前はピエロだ
You're a clown.
And you see? There's a girl in that dark corner with lonely eyes.
ほぉら
あんな暗いところに寂しげな目をしている女の子がいるよ
Oh no, you're right!
あ～　いけない　本当だ
僕が笑わせてあげっ
I'll make you smile-
Ooyama!
大山
お前最低な
You're horrible, you know that?
You've got it all wrong, Otonashi-san.
音無君　違うんですよ
Please listen to me, it was just some playful words.
聞いてください　言葉の綾です
次は僕が行きますから
I'll be sure to go next.
おい　だれかなんか言ってやれよ
Hey, someone say something for him.
いや　アタシ名前知らないですし
But I don't even know his name.
Let's go.
行きましょう
Passage to the Guild B15
Just how many is this?
これで何体目よ
I don't know. I quit counting already.
わかんねえ
もう数えてねえよ
This time, I'll be going.
今度こそ俺が行く
Hold on! I'm up before you.
待て
俺の番だ
You stay on your feet until the last one.
お前は最後まで残れ
Why?
なぜ
She's waiting for you.
あの子はお前を待ってる
そんな気がするからだ
I just know she is.
That's why you have to go on.
だから　お前は進むんだ
Okay? Also, if-
いいな
あともしッ
If you're gonna go, get going already!
行くんならとっとと行けや
Wait for me, Senpai.
待ってて　先輩
Do you like him or do you hate him?
お前　あいつのこと好きなのか　嫌いなのか
着いたわね
Here we are.
Ground Zero of the Guild.
「ギルト」爆破の跡
Ground Zero
Deepest Recess of the Guild
We'll be going all the way down to the deepest recess from here.
ここから一気に最下層に降りることになるわ
音無君とユイはオリジナルを探して
Otonashi-kun and Yui, you two look for the original.
見つけ次第　「ハーモニックス」の発動を促すこと
As soon as you find her, tell her to use Harmonics.
俺が戦ったほうがいい
I should be the one doing the fighting.
Don't you remember what Hinata-kun said?
日向君も言ったでしょう
あの子はアナタを待っているのよ
She's waiting for you.
In that case, I'll fight.
じゃあ　アタシが戦います
弱すぎて話にならない
You're so weak, you're out of the question.
話にしてくださいよ
Take me into consideration, please!
じゃ行くわよ
All right, let's go.
いや　むちゃ強いですから
No, see, I'm actually really strong.
I hope this will be our last operation.
これが最後の作戦になるといいわね
Yeah.
だな～
あ～　待ってくださいよ
Please wait!
あれ　ユイは
Huh? Where's Yui?
I heard a very short scream from her.
なんか短い悲鳴だけ聞こえたが
Did she fall to Tenshi's hand?
天使の餌食か
Poor thing. But we'll save her soon.
可哀相に
でもすぐ助けてあげるわ
また生き残ったのはこの二人ね
So, yet again, only we survived to the end.
そうだな
Yeah. Just like last time.
前回と一緒だ
そろそろ最後かしら
Is this the last one, I wonder?
そう願いたいが
I sure hope so.
ほら　あんたはぼうっとしてないでオリジナルを探せ
Hey, now. Stop standing there and search for the original.
R-Right!
んぅ　あ
やっぱり
Figures.
Damn, she's tough.
くそ　しぶとい
Plug your ears!
耳を塞いで
Guard Skill: Howling.
ガードスキル「ハウリング」
なんだ　これ
What is this?!
My ears!
耳が
You weren't... knocked out?
気絶…しない
ええっ　なんて
Oh, what's that? What did you say?
I have plugs in my ears, so I can't hear you very well.
耳栓してるから　よく聞こえないのよ
Give it up.
ほら　観念なさい
なんなら　もう一本のナイフで喉を掻っ切ってあげるわよ
If you prefer, I'll slit your throat with my other knife.
いた
There she is!
奏
Kanade!
大丈夫か
Are you all right?
Yes.
うん
The Battlefront's here to save you with everything we've got.
戦線の皆がな命を張ってお前を助けに来たんだ
そう
I see.
Oh, right. Kanade, I'm sorry to ask when you're so worn out, but I need you to use one of your skills.
そうだ　奏　無理させて悪いが
一つ能力を使ってほしいんだ
「ハーモニックス」だ
Harmonics.
If you use it, everyone will be saved.
使ってくれたら皆が助かる
I see, okay.
そう
分かった
Will you last even if you use it?
使っても体は持つか
うん　一回ぐらいなら
Yes, if it's just once.
ガードスキル「ハーモニックス」
Guard Skill: Harmonics.
プログラムの書き換えをしたようね
It seems you rewrote the program.
ああ
Yeah. They'll all return to her.
すべてこいつの中に戻る
あれだけの数の冷酷なアタシたちが？
So that many ruthless versions of me will combine?
どういうことだ
What do you mean?
The clones have their own mind.
分身にだって意識はあるの
It's not that they will disappear. They'll simply fuse as part of her.
それは消えてしまうわけじゃない
同化するの
アナタたちを襲ったたくさんのアタシたちが
All those versions of me that attacked you will fuse back into her.
この子の中に戻るの
And do you really think nothing will happen to her after suddenly fusing with so many like-minds?
それだけの意識を一度に吸い込んでしまって
ただで済むと思う
時間ね
It's time.
Wait!
待ってくれ
Shit...
くそ
Please hang in there...
無事でいてくれ
...Kanade!
奏！！
I've always walked this path alone; when I look back, everyone is so far away.
itsumo hitori de aruiteta furikaeru to minna ha tooku
いつもひとりで歩いてた　振り返るとみんなは遠く
いつも一人で歩いてた
振り返るとみんなは遠く
●
それでも私は歩いたそれが強さだった
Even so, I kept on walking. That was my strength.
soredemo atashi ha aruita sore ga tsuyosa datta
それでもあたしは歩いた　それが強さだった
．
●
"Nothing frightens me any longer", I mumble softly.
mou nanimo kowakunai sou tsubuyaitemiseru
もう何も恐くない　そう呟いてみせる
もう何も 怖くない
そうつぶやいてみせる
いつか　人は一人になって
．
Eventually, everyone ends up alone,
itsuka hito ha hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
．
And is left with only their memories.
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
In order to appreciate even sorrow and continue smiling,
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ愛し笑ってられるように
．
I'll keep on fighting,
atashi ha tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
私は戦うんだ
I won't show you my tears.
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
Next Episode Preview
What will happen to us?
We've never seen Tenshi like that before.
But that was only a temporary measure.
I'd say we have a 1% chance.
Do you intend to undress me?
What the hell is this...?
Someone punch him!
Let's all survive through this!
No one's going to live through this!
Am I going to disappear?
Whose side will God take?
Come back!
Otonashi...
I remember everything now.